Hi everybody. Here again for another
release roundup. This week I've got four
exciting ones. First up we've got
installing skills globally. So not every
skill that you want to use. It makes
sense to install in a single repo.
Sometimes you have [music] personal
workflows or preferences, things that
span multiple projects. [music] Now with
Tesla, you can install your skills
globally and they'll be shared across
all of your projects and you don't have
to worry about disrupting your teammates
workflows.
Second, we've got watch local. This is a
new command line flag for working with
Tessle. If you're ever in the process of
developing a skill that you've installed
in many agents, you've probably felt the
pain of making a [music] change, copying
it over to every agents folder, then
restarting all of your sessions to load
the new changes. Now, with a watch local
flag, when you make a change to a skill
that you're working on with Tessle,
we'll automatically sync all those
changes across all of your agents.
Third, we've added GitHub badges for
your eval scores. So, if you've done the
work to make your skill truly excellent,
we now give you a way to add a badge to
your GitHub page, showing any potential
users the quality of your skill and
helping you sort of build confidence
that what you've done is worth
installing.
Finally, we've made a change to the way
we score skills on our registry. So, we
[music] have two types of evaluations.
We have reviews which check your skills
against standard best practices. And we
have task evals which will run agents
through simulated scenarios to measure
your skills impact on actual real world
results. We've now added a single
aggregate score that blends these two in
an intuitive single number that you and
your agents can look at when deciding
whether or not a skill is right for your
workflows. That's it for now. We'll be
back soon with more exciting updates.